And we are live. Welcome back everyone
in the chat.
What's up, Mitchell? How are you doing?
>> Yes, good. How are you?
>> Um um token maxing right now, like
crazy.
>> [laughter]
>> On every account?
>> Oh, yes. Uh yeah. I I I'm trying to save
some tokens for the rest of the week,
but uh can't wait for Friday, but not to
go to weekend. Just to reset my Claude
accounts.
>> So, if you analyze like the Claude X and
uh Claude data, they think you have like
a 10-people company.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. And also like today I I created a
uh skill in Claude X to have the
equivalent of Claude Ultra Claude mod.
So, I'm
going
>> So, there there is a trick. Ultra Claude
is just a skill.
>> So, for Claude X, right? Because of
Claude Ultra Claude it's basically X I
plus workflows and slash sub agents.
>> Mhm.
>> So, if you have a skill that does that
with Claude X until they implement it,
and maybe 5.6, I hope 5.6 would have it.
Yeah.
Then
that's going to be late. But, I'm
once I'm going to end up the weekly
My bad.
>> No problem.
>> But, Mike [laughter]
Uh once I'm going to max out the weekly
on my account, then I will try the truck
on mode with Codex.
And uh, it's going to be fun, but yeah,
that's what I want.
>> See how good that is.
>> Yeah, because right now for me like
Codex 5.5 is dumb as [__]
>> Well, I still use it on the on the
smaller task.
>> Yeah.
And maybe I should do that, but I don't
have small
>> That saves you some room because setting
up a full workflow
>> [laughter]
>> and changing a a background color,
that's a bit too much.
>> No, but I dropped the beta issues like
the whole P&D. Like right this week I've
done a lot of P&D implementation and
okay, also refactoring like some
workflow workers
so that took a lot.
And split it from the API
call to from the
to have a
another microservices.
>> Okay, cool. So so you're rebuilding the
entire app again.
>> No, okay. So no okay, so wait.
It's not for Genfit, it's for like a
customer, but um
I started to work on the workers
implementation and I checked after what
was the initial implementation and it
merged the API and the workers service
together and I don't want that. I want
a clean separation of the API and the
workers. So I moved some files away.
>> Okay, cool.
>> And that's also I think what it took a
lot of tokens.
Uh, yeah. I have a task that's taken
about 2 million tokens output, but yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> What about At least you're you're maxing
it out.
>> Oh, oh yeah. Oh yeah. I'm maxing it.
I'm scrapping every token out of the
uh
out of the weekly subscription for sure.
What about you, man? What did you do
this week?
>> Uh, yeah, a lot of coding and I enjoyed
the good weather.
>> Oh, yeah. The weather is good.
>> but like four agents are running, right?
>> True.
But like uh do you do you have like a
hot weather hot chemical you know
chemical hot stuff?
>> No, no, no. We just set up the pool in
the garden and that's it.
>> Oh, nice.
Okay. Nice.
Oh, yeah.
>> So,
and then let the AI's work.
>> Yes.
Bringing the money home.
>> So, you can buy a pool. Yeah.
>> [snorts]
>> And next year you can like ask someone
to set up the pool for you.
>> Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> See if you can rent an AI to do it.
>> Yeah, exactly. Yeah, well soon soon then
we'll have a boat.
>> That would be cool.
>> Yeah, yeah. Okay, so we're going to talk
about loops so we can max out your
subscription, man.
>> Yes, because I still didn't use them. Is
that bad?
>> The loops?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, yeah. So, okay, we're going to
talk about that but loops or basically
basically cron jobs to trigger AI agent
aka open claw
smart trigger stuff that we had six
months ago. Now, we have a term for that
which is loops aka cron jobs.
>> Yes.
It is just keep on repeating until it
works perfectly.
>> Basically, yes. But okay, let me let me
do the introduction. Yes. So,
should be fun.
Uh, it's going to be a good one.
Okay.
Are you maxing out
I'm going to do that.
>> [laughter]
>> Rewind.
>> Okay.
Are you maxing out your
Are you maxing out your subscription?
Not yet? So, start triggering loops
automation for Cloud and no,
routing for Cloud and
automation for CodeX. Is that it? Am I
right? Or did I reversed it?
Wait, let me check.
AI transcript.
Uh
Claude is slash loop.
>> Yes. Yes. So, routines for
uh routines for Claude and automation
for codex.
>> I got it. I got it. I got it.
I got it. Let me Okay.
So, take
>> Let's go. It's going to be a good one.
Uh AI
uh
Cut from here for the introduction.
Cuz I have an MCP to edit, so that's
nice.
>> Are you maxing out your subscription?
No, not yet. So, start looping. Start
Loop Engineering.
Set up uh Claude automation. No, [__]
And start Claude routines or codex uh
automations and
um
implement some task uh autonomously.
Yes? Let's go.
>> Let's go.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, that's that's a hard introduction.
Um
and if you want to know
how to set up your loops,
uh watch this video because we have some
tools for you.
And what? Subscribe. Thank you.
Okay.
>> We show you how to build a loop, to
create your loop, and keep checking a
loop.
>> I mean, you can do that actually. Like
uh yeah.
>> Because okay, so right now for you, what
did you do with like those automation
routines, loop stuff, or even slash loop
in Claude or even slash goal with codex?
>> Yeah, well, I've been using those kind
of setups for a long time, but I never
use them like slash loop.
I even just have some of my own systems
that just keep on repeating.
>> Yeah.
I I yeah.
>> And it's easy.
>> So I mean
>> To be honest, there is a lot of hype and
if you don't use it, you can improve a
lot, but
it's not totally new.
>> That I mean, ooh.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
Okay, thank you.
>> Um yeah, I think it came from like Peter
and like Evan Open Claw because he
started like some tweets. We're going to
show that now.
>> I mean, he's
in the interview.
>> Tag.
Peter Standberger.
So tag, puff.
Where it was
uh
It was like a day
weekly monthly reminder like here's
simple loop like I how to use loops and
how to basically set them up in clicks.
All right, one example at least. Uh tell
Kodak to maintain your repos, wake up
every 5 minutes and direct work on
thread that make it easy to paralyze
plus tier work as needed. Uh yeah.
I use an orchestrator skill combined
with my triage plus auto review computer
plus computer use skills so some work
can land autonomously.
And
yeah.
Like
>> Do these loops still cause a lot of
tokens because we had the Ralph loops
and uh Open Claw had the same ones. It
has a cron job in the background that
just keeps on checking and every time
even if there is nothing to do, you burn
tokens.
>> That's why you need like a safe stop if
it loops
again and again. It's kind of like you
know when you have like
usage
based
billing and then you have spent 200
Amazon AWS credits. You just don't know
why, but you forgot
an instant that's running in since
forever.
>> Yes.
>> Like
>> You still have to back up of your
database running.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, exactly. No, it's it's still
tricky, but I mean for cleaning up a
repo
uh
like that makes sense. Like you you can
even like delete your branch or even
for me like if
work tree is merged on master, then I
delete the work tree and I have a daily
cron/automation
doing that. And it also clean up the the
remote origin like the GitHub repo.
And you can have that for pull request,
too.
>> Mhm.
>> Like on a open source project, you can
have a daily pull request reviewer like
ultra code or whatever and then it can
check all of the pull request and then
you merge like safely what's
it's team wants to be
integrated to the
>> Yeah.
>> project. So, it's helping you in the
bigger project to maintain everything.
>> I think so, yeah. And even like for me
like when I have like 20 pull request to
review, I just like ever have a loop
ready to I can automation. Like it's
kind of weird to buy like for me when
people say loop, it's like almost a
while
one equal one just burn tokens.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. And as long as it's
below 10, keep on going.
>> Yeah. And like what the Yeah, it's
exactly. And uh
what we talked about last week was when
also it was expensive because we don't
have like free tokens anyway like Peter.
And that's why he spent like 1.3 mil on
who God knows what.
Uh
because he has unlimited access to
Codex.
>> Yeah, he can just have the
the bot check every minute is there a
task active yes or no.
>> He said that he said that he had
every pull request is like reviewed
multiple times.
>> [clears throat]
>> Mhm. Um
by by 5.5.
>> Yeah.
>> So like
it's not really applicable right now.
Okay, so another
Like this is becoming my
is building another software like blood
clot at SH to read Twitter. Let's go.
Uh
people are discussing what happened with
open clot. The hype died down. We
improve quality and grow a team and
created non-profit where the competition
Yeah, like a more and more people are
using MS now.
Uh multimodal routing
>> Oh, yeah. You did you see that like the
a new Japanese model that is multimodal
routing that use multimodal routing as a
features to uh kind of like open router
auto but it's coming from
Japanese labs.
>> Yeah, that was the startup, right? Or
was it a different one?
>> Like the Suko
Uh where is it?
Yes, Sakana.
>> Yeah, that one.
>> Yes, they they got 20 million. That's
crazy.
They pushed that yesterday. That could
be interesting to follow up. We can
follow up on that
next week, I think.
Maybe we can
add this stream blog. Yep.
>> Let's see what what people created and
what they did on checks and benchmarks
and everything.
>> Yeah, we can talk about that next week.
But
that could be also an interesting for us
if we use like both Codex, Claude and
stuff. Maybe there is something to do
with that. Could be the next uh the next
meta next week.
Uh okay. So, uh buff
>> As long as we don't have 5.6 for Codex
this week, I think that will do a lot.
>> Yes. And yeah, and again, I have if we
have workflow on 5.6, that would be
sick. Um
it's supposed to drop this week, right?
>> Mhm.
>> I seen people saying Thursday.
>> Oh.
>> Who knows?
>> Okay.
And we will have like limit reset too.
That's going to be fun.
Uh okay. So, loop explain Is that not
the article we read last week?
>> Yes.
>> [__]
Damn. Forgot about that.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh how most people use AI yeah most yeah
okay. That was the That was the tweet I
mentioned like here you're mostly
reminded that you should not be
prompting coding agent anymore. You
should be designing loops that prompt
your agent.
Uh
[__] I took again like the same
source.
Damn.
Okay. Yeah, that's exactly the same
thing. Um
but also since then
I have another repo.
Uh
Where is it?
Uh so, I built my own repository with my
own loops.
Like as a template, but where is
>> Like a loop database.
>> Yes.
Uh for what feature? Yes. Loop library.
And mine back.
So,
from
What's his name again? Yes. Matt Berman.
>> [clears throat]
>> Do do do.
Back. Uh
I want to find him
first.
Damn.
Uh
Codex Loop. Oh, yeah. Yeah,
that was a good fix.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Uh tag Okay, so this one we don't care
about that because that's a semantical
in last week. That's my bad, but
Where is he?
Yes.
So, Matthew Berman, he's a YouTuber like
AI YouTuber.
And he shared his uh Loop Library
um to like set up automation
routines in uh yeah, code and Codex.
And
like the uh yeah, the last one the lazy
loops, I I can discover Discover will uh
will uh look through your code base and
start straight to find potential loops.
It will design for you. It's kind of
like a skill creator stuff,
but on the loops. So, if you drop that
into your uh code base, that should be
I'm pretty sure there is some stuff that
you can
um
implement as a loop.
>> Okay, that's cool.
>> Yeah, and his library
uh Loop Library, what's a loop?
Why loop a powerful AI agent can move
quickly, but an open
open-ended instruction like keeping
improving this leaves too much room for
guessing. A loop give gives the work a
clear finish line and a consistent way
to judge progress.
>> Mhm.
>> That makes the work easier to trust and
easier to repeat. Yeah, again, like you
need a self uh
a safe end state.
>> Yeah, you need boundaries.
>> Yep.
Uh so, what's the Loop Library skill
does? Uh give you your agent direct
access to the uh to the IDs in the
library.
Uh discover repeated work in the code
base um coding thread and all those
internal stored qualified candidate into
a loop.
Find a published loop that fits uh what
you are doing to get down audit an
existing loop for weak checks. Adapt the
useful loops. Design a new loop new
a new loop through a short and plain
language conversation. Turn the result
into a compact prompt.
Okay, install I want the list of loops.
Discover find loop doctor. Okay, audit a
loop you passed. Okay, adapt tell or
useful to you real tools. And design so
that's exactly what I read.
Uh
Okay.
Where is it?
Oh, it's not even
Oh.
Okay, it's even different than I
imagined. It's uh
Okay, that's pretty smart. I thought it
was a
a list of loops he was using which is
what I've done. But it's not it's
something Okay, it's something smarter
than what I thought because that dynamic
you drop that and then
you get the loops that you need.
>> Yeah, so it actually analyzes your code.
>> Yes.
That's cool.
Oh, yeah. Okay, no. Okay, so then I
Okay, there's something I don't
understand
because that's the loops. Yeah, copy
loops. The full product evaluation loop,
the 5-minute repository maintainer, the
refund follow-up loop, get my refund for
Oh, okay.
Get my refund for company and charging
for start the claim now. Okay, latex
document bro latex.
Never use that.
The one post week one post a week loop
find a reliable weekly post format from
approve account. Through a 6-week
experiment.
Oh, people are Okay, okay, okay. So, he
used a tool to discover the loops and
then you have a
a
for people to post their own loops.
>> That's cool.
Future proof.
>> Yeah, and those are working like
templates, right?
>> Yeah, no, exactly.
Um
Copy the loop, build sanitize production
scale local data under production like
settings, inventory, every user facing
feature, role button, root button input
model state,
define documented acceptance criteria,
and
finish risk-based edge case for each
test as a real user logging every bug
with reproduction evidence.
Wait, what?
Oh, inventory product product surface
meets its documented acceptance
criteria. Okay, that's cool. I mean,
okay, that makes sense if you have a
good
user storyboard.
>> Mhm.
>> Is that something that you would drop in
a repo that you have for a customer?
>> Not without proper testing, but
the question is, I want to run it
because if you don't know and it keeps
on looping and it keeps on making
mistakes, it can be either very
expensive
or just mess up everything.
And that's like one of the experiences I
had with Ruby. I said, "Just keep on
improving."
>> Mhm.
>> It had [clears throat] a bug. It looped
it. It had to change something else
uh to fix the bug, but that created
another bug, and eventually it just kept
on looping on fixing bugs.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you either need
good boundaries like we just said or a
very good preparation, but people who
think that the loops are just something
that you add and it creates the perfect
system, I don't believe that's true.
>> Yeah. I mean, like okay, so
uh
since the age of AI development,
uh you need to be really good at product
management.
Like you need to really have good user
stories and
like
Yeah,
be clear with the architecture that you
have in mind and like to know where
you're going.
Because yes, like the AI can code, but
the AI will code crappy [__] if you
don't have
a GitHub view issues or PRDs and
whatever, right?
>> Yeah.
>> It will just
do everything to accomplish the task
that you gave it without additional
subtasks.
>> Yeah.
No, exactly. And even more if you don't
have a
deterministic
end state of the loop.
Because I watched the video like okay,
no, I watched the video and then I drop
it in the in the transcript to to code,
but for example, for Matt uh yeah, Matt,
right?
Yeah, for Matthew,
he talked about the loop stuff and he
said, "Okay, so I have a loops that are
deterministic, but also
AI based where it tell the agents that
um
until do XYZ until it's
uh
acceptable.
>> Yeah, but that's
>> What does it mean?
>> Yeah.
>> So, yeah, I would rather have a loop
that okay, reach
uh 80%
coverage or run for 2 hours.
>> Yeah.
What?
I think that's the same thing like
telling your kid you can watch TV when
you're done yeah, cleaning the house and
the cleaning needs to be acceptable.
>> Yeah.
>> So,
they will just vacuum like the whole
that's it and go watch TV.
>> Yeah.
I mean, yeah, and so the accept the
acceptance criteria would be until I I I
say so.
Yeah. Yeah. So,
>> You can set up the loop and it can do a
lot of work, but the preparations need
to be properly done. You need to know
exactly what you want, how you want
that, how secure does it need to be,
what happens if A, what happens if B,
and you can still do that discussing it
with the AI, but
>> Mhm.
>> you cannot just trust that the loop
makes all the right decisions.
>> Yes, but that Okay, so yeah, I I agree
with that, but like for example, I have
automation that grab
um
a GitHub issue every four every four
hours between 10:00 p.m. and 6:00 a.m.
So, it runs three times, so I can
monitor it in the morning. And it also
like take
um
a feature to implement
that is already on the GitHub board
and with a special label on it.
>> Yeah, so you you approved it up front.
>> Yes, exactly. And then it's like
secondary features or stuff like that,
and it's it's working only when I'm not
working myself.
Yeah. So,
like it's a good compromise and then I
can reduce like the the time frame
between like two backlog pick up or
yeah, or even like
do that multiple multiple times with
other project and stuff like that. Um
but if the That's why like the GitHub
board is my
IDE, you know? Like
>> Mhm.
>> And I clean the GitHub board and the
GitHub issues every week and almost
every day I do like a proper clean up.
>> Yeah, but you can also create a loop
that just takes any bugs that are
registered and ask it to only add a
solution.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you can approve it up front.
>> Yeah, like you Yeah, you have the pull
request open and I don't have any loop
that auto merge anything because I want
to have a clear view of every pull
request
that I have open.
>> Yes.
Exactly.
>> Right. Yeah, I don't want to merge
anything that I don't have a I don't
if I don't know the title of the pull
request or I don't know what's going on.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, not exactly. And I I've created
like a stand-up skill, which is like
give me the all of the commit summary of
the last 7 days, 24 hours, whatever. Um
so
I have that, too.
>> Okay, that's cool. Yeah, that's nice.
>> And yeah, I can show you because I have
the repo on GitHub. Everything is on
GitHub because uh
>> [clears throat]
>> it's cool.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh okay.
>> Eventually, you're just a team lead with
your AI team.
>> Mhm,
100%.
100%. So, that's my Vincent ship sits
loops rip uh repo
where uh yeah, clean template and prompt
from Codex automation, cloud routines,
and recurring agent uh loops.
Blah blah blah, copy paste, install your
prompt. Yeah, so you you drop that to
your agent and it will um set up the
uh loops for you.
>> Mhm.
>> [clears throat]
>> So, the list of loops that I have,
automation path, code hygiene, uh
content factory maintenance, uh which is
tag
uh improve the project content docs,
prompt, and skill pipeline with one uh
small high-leverage maintenance pass.
So, yeah, also reduce the size of the
scope of the loop. Like, I want the loop
to touch like five, 10 files max and not
do a full
uh crazy stuff.
Um so, that Yeah, feature
implementation, that's what I was
talking about.
Uh implement exactly one read ready
issue from the canonical project board.
And uh, so everything is on GitHub. You
go You check the board. You check the
pull request. Boom.
Uh, work tree hard pull uh, GPT-5
uh, excite work tree boom all of that.
And you can drop all of that routines
and boom it's ready to go.
>> That's cool.
>> Yeah, and it's edge on first. So, yeah,
it's cool. Uh, sentry out fix recent
commit review.
Um, I just like yeah, double check all
of the commits and yeah, review new
commits on the GitHub repo master since
the last successful review baseline or
the last 24 hours.
Uh, when the baseline exists. Uh,
uh, fix only high confidence issues.
>> Love it.
>> And uh,
tag and for Claude do I have anything
different?
Link example schedule task board hygiene
dry refactor.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's also a loop
that I like.
Um,
perform one small dry refactor in
project. So, take whatever you want in
the repo, make it better, dry it up.
Boom.
And that's it's not Okay, it's a ultra
code 4.8 stuff, but uh, it's works
pretty well. Uh, work tree prune. So,
that's what I was saying like once
every day, I think.
>> Mhm.
>> [clears throat]
>> Um,
Oh, there is not the time here. Okay.
Um,
Yeah, prune merge local work tree and
branch for project. Uh, work only for
the repo GitHub repository. Do not
inspect modify summarize out of scope
project.
Fetch and prune remote never delete the
main checkout current branch and merge
work dirty work trees or branches with
unpushed commit. Only remove work trees
whose branch are our merged into masters
or whose PR are merged.
>> Mhm.
>> And then I I I I
I get like a gigabyte
on my computer back because walk through
your something else.
And uh yeah, stuff like that.
Uh react nightly expansion, yes, I like
this one.
Uh so, I have um
I have
uh nightly job
where I can increase the end-to-end uh
pass on the apps I work on and uh I just
increase the coverage of the end-to-end
and that's automation is doing it, too.
>> That sounds good. So, how much of your
work are you doing with loops right now?
>> Uh so,
I mean, some of them.
Uh I still like
uh work like she all day and I'm maxing
out my subscription, but uh I have like
So, right now on one account, I have
four of six
uh workflow. So, basically like the the
one I said uh
for cloud, it's it's more advanced uh
tech.
Uh I have the board hygiene, the bundle
side watchdog, I don't have it. It's
probably like a
uh
still. Dry refactor, feature
implementation, nightly end-to-end,
uh
react fix pass, not really. Repro agent
cleanup work. Or probably Okay, I'm
going to redo that because it So, it
sounds duplicate.
Uh security fix pass, no. And uh walk
through print. So, yeah, I have like
four to six
um loops per project that will help me
maintain the GitHub board
and uh my local host computer and
implement some secondary features.
Basically.
So, I'm going slow because again, I need
my subscription to last another week.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Otherwise, you have like a few days off.
>> Yeah.
>> But, honestly, like, I don't know what's
best of like between
having those kind of loops and it's
operates by itself, and then you can
have a new loop
like a feature implementation every 30
minutes.
Like, if you have the full um user story
on your GitHub, what's
uh
uh what's the problem of starting this
uh loop every 30 minutes if you have the
token and the
uh allocation for it?
>> Yeah, you can just finish everything.
>> Exactly.
Which is not because it never happened
before.
Like
>> You always had a huge backlog.
>> Exactly. You can't
clean up a GitHub board pretty eye.
>> No.
Yeah, unless you have like a big-ass
expensive team.
>> I'm pretty [snorts] sure Amazon never
[__] clean up
>> No.
>> [snorts]
>> Like, expensive or not, that's uh
Because yeah, because you keep logging
stuff faster than you can better But,
again, again, like as a dev, like uh you
are PM and your job is to have a always
a GitHub issue ready for clothes to pick
up.
>> Yeah, that makes sense. You pay for it,
so why not use it?
>> Exactly, 100%. And so, is that like like
Do you see like uh
yourself working with that? Like, does
that make sense even for your use case
when
>> Yeah, on bigger projects, it does. But,
when you have multiple customers and you
do small issues, it's easier to just do
one prompt, push it, and be done.
>> Mhm. Like, do you see that it as a goal?
>> Uh the the one prompt?
>> Like Like yeah, like the slash goal do
that and don't stop until it's done.
>> No, no, I I never did.
>> Yeah.
And um
do you Yeah.
So, basically the customers give you all
this is broken or I need that and then
you give it the
like the features and then job done and
then you go to the next customer?
>> Yes.
And and sometimes you're just working on
multiple ones because you're doing
research on one and you have the second
one which you're working on your
project.
>> Mhm.
And
is there a way for you to have like
proactive plans issues? Because then you
don't have a GitHub board or issues
ready to go at all, right? Because you
don't know what's going to come
>> No, it's more like a ticket system.
>> Yeah. Mhm.
>> So, you don't know and not everything is
is smaller websites are not in GitHub.
It It can be just a WordPress team.
>> Oh, yeah, yeah, okay, okay, okay.
>> Yeah,
you can spend a lot of time on on
setting it up and connecting everything,
but you only have like 2 hours of work
on that website each month. So, why set
it up in this big
>> Yeah.
>> expensive solution if you are not using
it.
>> Yeah, true.
Mhm.
>> So, it's even faster to just download it
by FTP and open cloud it in that folder.
>> Yeah.
Mhm.
Wait Oh, wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. You
don't have the WordPress on your local?
>> Yeah, you do, but you can just swap
teams and databases.
>> Swapped what?
>> Yeah, you have the local setup, but if
it is just some team or whatever, you
can just download the just some CSS. You
can just download the team.
>> Yes.
>> Or if it's bug fixing you need to find a
bug. You just download the team, check
it, and that's it.
>> Yeah, okay. Okay.
>> So, this is cool for bigger projects
where you have everything set up in
GitHub, but if you do a lot of work, I
still prefer prompting. And you can even
say, uh do a loop or hit a goal or
whatever, but
>> Yeah, okay.
>> Yeah.
>> That makes sense.
Yeah. Okay, because for you it's one
short steps. So, there's not even like
PM slash preparation of the board of the
issue. Uh that uh that's tricky.
>> Sometimes it's like 10 to 15 different
customers a day.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Okay. That's an interesting workflow.
So,
you would even Okay, so what about Okay,
I'm I'm looking for automation here. Uh
what about you have
a wrote an automation or code automation
that check your email,
and
it would scope
the issue, create a GitHub issue,
and uh directly from the email, and I
even start the implementation based on
the email
request. Or do you do back and forth
between the customers and yourself?
>> Well, I
uh I deleted Zendesk, and I did my own
my own ticket system. So, I have my
local Mac mini that copies my database
because I don't want it active in the in
the actual database.
So, it does a pull request, updates the
database once per hour, and I can just
say, "See ticket five, number five." And
read it, and it looks up the tickets in
my database, and it knows the exact
conversation and the issue, and it knows
what to do.
>> What ticket?
>> So, it is like a local setup on Mac
mini.
>> Does it start implementation by itself?
>> Um
I can have it do that because I have a
uh a
a table, a logging of what customer
number is
having a project in what folder. So, it
knows exactly if it is Vincent then go
to this folder and this is the project
we're talking about.
>> That's
>> So, it can actually I point it to a
ticket number
and if it can't find it, it will just
pull the database locally and it will
analyze the tickets that we did. It will
check the code and it will give me a
solution and then I can say, "Okay,
implement it or not." So, that's the
automation I have right now.
>> That's sick.
Because it's it's even like we thought a
fake cron job. It's like triggered on
event already.
>> Yeah.
>> Nice.
That's That's
>> That's also why I'm looking. Why do I
even want to build a get up and a loop
for something so small?
>> Yeah, I know exactly. Yeah, yeah, an
event like it's even like
based on an event. So, again, you don't
know what's going to come next, but like
for me I have a full road map of
features to implement and stuff to So, I
know what's coming up next and I can
organize the queue of task and once one
is done, bam, I push the next one.
>> Yeah. And only cool thing is when you
because we are actively managing, for
example, 50 WordPress themes
>> Mhm.
>> and I know what plugins are in what
WordPress. So, if you get a notification
of a leak or
security issue
>> Mhm.
>> I can just tell it, "Hey, this is the
list of all the websites. Check it." And
it just checks the code locally.
It gives me back which ones are
having issues and I can just deploy
automatically solutions to solve it.
>> Nice. That's cool. So, you have even
like a bit Yeah, it's a it's a next
version because again, it's event based.
>> Yeah.
>> So, it's even better than a cron job
that run every 5 minutes then bounce
token to check if there is something to
do.
You it's like a webhook stuff?
>> Yeah. And if I have a crunchable webhook
in it, it needs to check every minute if
there is an update, but I know because
I'm running it locally, I just have a
Python script that initiates a task. So,
the Python script is the crunchable and
scraping it and it will cost me zero
tokens.
>> Nice. I only trigger the AI when I need
to.
>> Yeah.
I see.
>> And then the AI is not allowed to
publish publicly, so it cannot push to
live. I have to do that manually right
now, but
>> That makes sense.
>> I think that's much better.
>> Yeah, I know. I mean, like your your use
case makes sense because like
yeah, you have big customers with like
production like live data, so yeah, you
need to you need to review what you're
going to push. Like for me, it's more
greener apps, so
uh
if there is a bug, I can fix it.
>> Yeah.
>> I can
>> And that was also the issue I had like
how am I going to check data from an
online database without accessing it and
have maybe a possibility that the AI
pushes a change to my database.
>> Mhm.
>> So, I just copy it locally.
>> That makes
>> something stupid, but it works.
>> Yeah. I mean, maybe that's an issue with
like the Wait, you have production data
on your local?
>> Yeah, I just pull a backup of my full
database every hour.
>> That's okay.
Yeah, that's good.
>> Even migrations, I can just test it
locally. Yes.
And if it works, I can push it live and
I'm absolutely certain I don't corrupt
any data. And if it goes wrong, I just
press the button, I download the data
again. And it's like a 1-minute
download.
>> Mhm. I have a GitHub action for that
that
it's it's a dry run the migration,
take a snapshot,
and then execute the
migration and then finish the
deployment.
>> Yes.
>> On GitHub. But uh yeah, I I don't trust
those migration stuff. Like those seed
stuff migration like it's
>> I have had issues with them.
So. [laughter]
>> Yeah, no [__]
Um
okay, so yeah, maybe we can wrap it up.
But uh okay, last I'm going to I'm going
to going to talk about this ship ship
skill repository quickly so we can make
a story about it.
Um okay, yes. So, we have pulled up
together uh the ship ship dev
skills repository and I have created so
the standup stuff
that I talk about. Uh
standup, yes.
So,
it's from the I think uh yeah, I stole
that from the Kiso yeah, see to Kiso
team kit.
>> Mhm.
>> where you have a recap of everything
that you have personally shipped in the
last uh
uh 7 days, but you can say whatever
whatever
>> you want.
>> Uh from the Git history.
So, that's cool. Yeah, turn your own Git
history into a short honest recap and
what you actually ship is a
inward-facing twin of a change log
generator because I had that before.
Um
Now, the change log generate the change
log for the release and this one is
giving me uh what I've done
uh from those day
uh date timestamp stuff.
Uh
so, I do that on my weekly call uh audit
infrastructure bug uh bug all of that is
like to create a GitHub issues that will
be a bug with like a clear format on the
PRD and stuff.
Uh tag
uh find the GitHub issues on of type
bugs from a description structure a
clear bug report blah blah blah.
Uh if I see something that is not
working. And then I can tell the agents
to fix it in the next work tree.
>> Yeah. So, you can even follow up the
loop with a different loop.
>> Exactly. Yes.
I love it.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh
code review uh
code review, I think that's a peer
review, right?
Uh code review, correctness, security
testing, whatever. Uh
security gate, I can convicting finding
only flag issues you're certain about.
Uh ambiguity, default to request
changes, structural concern, cohesion,
abstraction. Uh stack rule, burn,
tailwind, yeah. So, that's the tech
stack. Uh
a diff branch PR to review.
Yes, and it could be even like a full
code base, I think.
Security, data isolation, TypeScript,
database, all of that.
It's lit. Uh
stack and yeah, like you said, I can use
those skills into a a loop and then
uh
the magic happens. Because then you have
the guardrail from the skills and you
have the loop, boom.
>> Yes, and you can just follow up loop
with different loop, and it is just a
It's like a full factory creating a
product.
>> Exactly.
And uh at the end, you can run this loop
because uh you never know what the AI is
is doing. So,
uh you can just simplify and uh cleaning
up the mess.
And yeah, all of those skills for
GitHub, uh tech tech tech, linters, LLM
MCP.
Uh Next.js, that's the back end I used.
And PRD.js, all of those PRD stuff. Uh
PRD quality gate.
I have a format for the PRD to follow.
Uh well, from PRD on the issue body that
serve as one, must contain all of the
following section as a markdown heading,
executing, problem statement, goals,
functional requirement, acceptance
criteria, and verification plan. So, all
of my PRD follow that.
>> That's cool.
>> Yeah.
And uh yeah, and uh
I make also like I ask Claude and Codex
to make it like
agent agentic first so the agent it it's
also
it will help the agents to understand
what
what it's doing.
And like it's formatted the way it will
understand it the most. I probably I
should probably like uh
I don't like writing PRDs and then PRD
Does that make sense?
I I should rename. Yeah, that should
that should be that should start start
with same kind of of what uh writing
PRD. Yeah, okay, it's probably I need to
consolidate that. And ultra code Okay,
yes. I Yes, 4 hours.
That's my ultra code uh code skill. Run
a Codex on only high autonomy workflow
to for difficult coding task. Inspect,
plan, choose
uh direct workflow, delegated mode, use
bonded sub agent when useful, integrate
in the parents of thread, verify and
continue until done or generally
blocked. Use when invoked with ultra
code ultra code ultra code max maximum
depth.
Cool. And split across agent parallel
agent blah blah blah.
Uh discipline Codex workflow for science
Codex coding task. The skill is not uh
hiding hidden runtime background
services or Claude ultra code to go.
Um
Yeah. So, that's that's my ultra code
version of Claude ultra code for Codex.
>> Okay. Keep me updated to to know how it
works.
>> I will do that this week because I'm
I'm on my spot on Claude so
this skill needs to work.
>> Yes. And let's hope maybe even 5.6 has
then.
>> Yeah.
That would be cool. Yes, if 5.6 drop and
they have ultra code mode with workflow
I'm trashing that skill and I will
I will
give Sam Altman all of my code base.
>> Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Or maybe even do it with your skill and
with their workflow and see what gives
the best result. Otherwise, you can just
send your skill to him.
>> [laughter]
>> Bro.
>> Yeah.
This performs like 200% better.
>> Please check it.
>> Ish.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh okay. Okay. 47. Well, 3 minutes. 3
minutes. 3 minutes. I wanted to talk
about that, too, before we conclude.
Uh not this one. This one. This loop
automation is not inside of correct. Go
go over every single features on this
app. Create a user story with expected
behavior based on the code keep uh on
the code. Keep a single canonical
spreadsheet tracking all of the fit
feature status. When done, switch loop
to testing every user story and document
all errors. When done, fix every
logistical errors or UX errors. Test
every use case behavior against post
fix.
So, okay. That's probably [__] but uh
That's all of that's previous user story
stuff.
>> That sounds like way expensive in code
in tokens.
>> Yes, probably.
Uh 100 of user story being walked
through like it's nothing. Uh yeah.
183 user story. One of
105 page router, etc.
Yeah.
>> And still, eh, I've had so many issues
with his uh um
uh front end prompt. He says fix every
issue,
but even without issues, it sometimes
looks really bad. So, I always add take
a screenshot of every page that you
create, analyze it, and fix everything
that's not working properly.
>> Yeah. I mean, like, yeah, the screenshot
in the conversation thread, that's
really powerful, too. I loved it, too.
Yes, but uh okay. So, let's do the
conclusion because we have uh some
customer to serve anyway. So, let's go.
Uh okay, so are you going to loop?
Are you going to
>> to loop, yes.
On the bigger projects, I'm going to
loop and see.
>> And uh yeah, I hope you're going to max
uh token uh
token maxing your subscription every
week, man.
>> Yes. Just make the max of what you're
paying. If you are paying for for
millions of tokens, don't stop at 1,000.
>> If you're not burning 1 billion token
per day, you're not even coding, bro.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh or maybe if you want to
uh to burn those tokens,
uh you can take some ship ship project
uh open source project and uh give it
some prompt to it.
>> Yeah, and just improve it and push it
and let us see what we can do with it.
>> Yes, exactly. Okay,
uh Mitchell, thank you so much for your
time. Everyone in the chat, thank you,
and we will see you uh in the video
recap.
>> Yes.
>> Uh that's coming up in the next few
days.
Bye, everyone. Bye-bye.
>> Bye.